Anne Henrietta Martin Papers BANC MSS P-G 282
The Bancroft Library
- Correspondence, 1892-1951; box 1-19
  - General Correspondence, 1892-1951; Sub-Series 1; Boxes 1-12
    - National Woman's Party, 1916-1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      74 letters
    - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Company, Inc., 1915-1916; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Neilsen, Mrs. P.T., 1914-1916; 6 letters (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Nevada. Department of Education, 1912-1914; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Nevada. Department of State, 1912-1919; 5 letters (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Nevada. Educational Survey Commission, September 14-29, 1918; 3 letters (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Nevada. Industrial Commission, September 15-22, 1914; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Nevada State Historical Society, 1940-1946; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Nevada. Nye County, 1914-1916; 7 letters (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Nevada, University of, 1914-1950 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      28 letters, Some signed by A.W. Hendrick, Walter Clark, John O. Moseley, as Presidents and Frederick Tiraner, Dean College of Education
    - Nevada Equal Franchise Society, 1912-1918; 28 letters (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Nevada Woman Suffrage Association, January-May 1915; 4 letters (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - New York Evening Post, February-March 1915; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1915-1936; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Newlands, Frances Griffith, 1915-1916; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Nixon, Kate, 1912-1916; 5 letters (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Norcross, Adeline, 1916; 8 letters (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Norcross, F.H., 1912-1916; 9 letters (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Norton, Mrs. F.L., 1915; 4 letters (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Nutt, H.C., March 17-20, 1920; 2 letters (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - O (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, Joseph D., October 6-12, 1914; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - O'Toole, Mary, October 3-9, 1915; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - The Open Door, April-July 1929; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Orr, Mrs. Alex, 1912-1918; 12 letters (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Our World, August 1-2, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      2 letters. Signed by Malcom W. Davis, editor
    - P (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Pache, A.W., October-November 1916; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Park, Alice, 1913-1949; 20 letters (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Park, Maud Wood, 1914-1916; 7 letters (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Parks, James H., 1913-1914; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Patrick, E.J., 1919-1920; 6 letters (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Paul, Alice, 1914-1950; 77 letters (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Co., May 16-29, 1918; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - People's Mandate to Governments to End Wars, 1936-1941 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      33 letters. Signed by Gaeta Wold Boyer, Alice Dodge
    - Pierce, Vivian, February-March 1915; 3 letters (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Pittman, Key, 1914-1916; 16 letters (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Pincus, Jane, September-November 1916; 4 letters (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Pittman, Vail, 1914-1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      5 letters. Some signed as Governor of Nevada.
    - Poindexter, Miles, 1919-1920; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Pollitzer, Anita, 1946-1947; 10 letters (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Pye, Edith M., 1928-1929; 6 letters (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Quam, Thelma, 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - R (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Rankin, Jeannette, 1913-1914; 3 letters (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Reconstruction Magazine (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Reid, John T., January 13-24, 1919; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Reilly, Caroline I., 1911-1916; 3 letters (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - City of Reno, City Clerk (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - City of Reno, Office of the Mayor (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Reno Commercial Club (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Reno Evening Gazette, 1914-1918; 3 letters (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Republican National Committee, 1916-1919 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      13 letters. Signed by Alvin T. Hert, western manager, Harriet Vittum, William R. Wilcox, Will H. Hays and others.
    - Review of Reviews, July 22-24, 1922; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Rice, Marguerite, May-August 1916; 3 letters (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Richard, Mrs. George W., 1915-1916; 2 letters (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Richardson, Mrs. L.M., 1912-1913; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Rickey, Vivian, 1915-1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Riegel, Ella, 1916-1920; 12 letters (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Riggs National Bank, 1916-1918; 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Ringrose, Mary E., September-October 1914; 10 letters (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Riverside Mill Company, September-October 1916; 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Roberts, G.M., 1912-1913; 6 letters (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Rodman, Lillian A., 1916-1919; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, August 26-28, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      4 letters.
    - Rowe, Clara Louise, September-November 1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Rowlands, T.T., 1914; 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - S (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco Examiner, 1914-1919; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco Public Library, May-June 1943; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Sanders, Mrs. P.V., October 14-21, 1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Sanford, George L., 1914-1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Schindler, Pauline G., 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Schwimmer, Rosika, 1936-1947; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Szars, Blanche, October 8-18, 1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Seeds, William P., October 14-23, 1914; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Shaw, Anna Howard, 1913-1915; 25 letters (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Shaw, Pauline A., 1915-1916; 4 letters (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Shields, M.U., October 24-30, 1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - The Silver State, 1914-1918; 4 letters (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Sippy, Mabel, November 4-9, 1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Marguerite, February-December 1929; 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Mary Rozet, 1931-1932; 25 letters (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Norton, Mrs. H.L., 1914-1917; 4 letters (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Squires, Deliphine, 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Stack, Zilpha A., August-October 1929; 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Stanford University. Hoover Library, September-December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      4 letters. Signed by Nina Almond.
    - Stanford University, 1920-1945 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      12 letters. Some signed by Ray Lyman Wilbur, as president.
    - Stevens, Doris, 1916-1947 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      28 letters. Some signed by Ray Lyman Wilbur, as president.
    - Stickney, Mrs. F.O., 1912-1913; 6 letters (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Stoker, Lillian, October-November 1916; 2 letters (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - The Suffragist, 1914-1920; 6 letters (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Summerfield, Mrs. Sardis, July-October 1916; 6 letters (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Swartz, Ida M., 1914-1915; 4 letters (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Swasey, Mrs. F.B., April-May 1915; 3 letters (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - T (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Mrs. H.C., 1912-1919; 7 letters; 2 telegrams (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, February-March 1921; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Louise, 1912-1913; 13 letters (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Tolhurst, Joseph A., 1915-1916; 3 letters (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Transcontinental Scrip Bureau, October-November 1914; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Tremawan, Mrs. C.S., April-October 1914; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Trend, January-February 1914; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Troendle, Lina E., August-October 1929; 3 letters (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Tummulty, Joseph Patrick, 1916-1918 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      2 letters. One written as Secretary to President Woodrow Wilson
    - Turner, Catherine, July 9-11, 1936; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - U (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - United Nations, 1949-1950; 15 letters (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - United States Department of Labor, Children's Bureau, 1918-1944 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      11 letters. Some signed by Katherine Lenroot
    - Upton, Harriet Taylor, 1914-1915; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - V (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Van der Seith, Emma, 1913-1915; 4 letters (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Vernon, Mabel, 1914-1950 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      101 letters. General letters to Anne Martin.
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1929-1941 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      5 letters. One written as editor of The Nation
    - Virginia Evening Chronicle, October 14-27, 1914; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Vose, Julia T., 1914-1919; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - W (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Walker, R.G., March-April 1919; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Walser, Margaret, 1914-1915; 3 letters (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Washoe County, Nevada, February-March 1914; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Washoe County Bank, 1918-1920; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Washoe County Library, 1945-1948; 2 letters (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Webb, Jonathan E., 1918-1919; 6 letters (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Webster, Gertrude, 1913-1916; 13 letters (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Weed, Helena Hill, 1916-1917; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Wells Fargo and Company, August-September 1914; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - West, Edith B., 1912-1914; 7 letters (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - West Virginia Equal Suffrage Association, 1915-1916; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Western Nevada Miner, March-October 1914; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Western Union Telegraph Company, February-May 1914; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - White, Gracie H., 1916-1919; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - White, Mary Ogden, February-May 1915; 3 letters (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - The White Company, September 9-24, 1914; 3 letters (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Whiting, E. H. and Company, March-December 1918; 9 letters (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Whitney, Charlotte Anita, February-March 1915; 6 letters (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Whittemore, Margaret Fay, 1916-1919; 21 letters (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Whittemore, Marjory, 1916-1930; 3 telegrams (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Williams, Mrs. George B., 1916, undated; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Williams, Mary Wilhelmine, 1936-1941; 6 letters (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Wilson, Bird M., 1912-1918; 70 letters (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Wilson, Carrie E., 1912-1916; 4 letters (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - WIlson, J. Stitt, August-October 1914; 5 letters (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Winter, Alice R., 1917-1918; 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - The Woman Citizen, July-September 1922 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      2 letters. One letter addressed to Ernest Gruening referring to an article Anne Martin Wrote for the Nation
    - Woman's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1920-1936 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      59 letters. Some signed by Lucy Biddle Lewis and Dorothy Detzer
    - Woman's Journal, 1911-1916 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      51 letters. Some letters signed by Alice Stone Blackwell and Agnes Ryan
    - Woman's Peace Party, March-May 1915; 4 letters (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Women's Social and Political Union, 1910-1911; 31 letters (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Wood, Mrs. H.C., 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Wyse, Cornelia, October-November 1916; 8 letters (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Y (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Yeager, Marie, 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Yerington, Ella L., 2 letters (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Young, Mabel, November 2-8, 1916; 3 telegrams (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Young, S.R., October 24-29, 1916; 3 telegrams (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Younger, Maud, 1912-1919; 17 letters (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Zadow, Sophia, 1914-1916; 6 letters (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Zimmerman, C.V. (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1892-September 1916 (Box 11, Folder 1-12)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, October 1916-1950 (Box 12, Folder 1-30)
  - Campaign Correspondence, 1918-1919; Sub-Series 2; Boxes 13-16
    - A (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Ackermann, Frances B., March-December 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Adamson, Ethel McClintock, March-April 1918; 3 letters (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Addams, Jane, March-September 1918 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      8 letters. Four letters signed by Eleanor Daggett Karsten.
    - Allender, Nina E., March-June 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Arnold, Virginia, September-October 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Aston, Ann Penn, September-December 1918; 6 letters (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - B (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Bakewell, Mary E., March 5-21, 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Baumann, Sophia E., March-November 1918; 5 letters (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Belches, Olive Mills, March-April 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Blatch, Harriet Stanton, March 1918-January 1919; 9 letters (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Boeckel, Florence Brewer, April-October 1918; 4 letters (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Bott, Rosina, June-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Boyle, Emmet, October 1-7, 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Brady, Ramona, September-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Breeze, Rita, October 7-13, 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Bright, Emily H., May 20-26, 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Brown, Olympia, March-April 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Byers, G.A., October 24-30, 1918; 3 telegrams (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - C (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Cannon, Laura Greff, April-May 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Cathcart, Mrs. James H., August-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Chandler, J.H., April-November 1918; 4 letters (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Condon, Mollie, May-November 1918 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      36 letters. Some addressed to Emma Nolan, Katherine Lincoln and Mabel Vernon.
    - Cooley, Winnifred Harper, July-October 1918; 6 letters (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Cuthbert, Gertrude, March-September 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - D (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Dick, C.J., June-July 1918; 2 letters and 1 typed copy (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - E (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Edwards, Elizabeth D. Morrill, April-December 1918; 5 letters (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Elko Free Press Publishing Company, March-July 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Ewing, Lucy, April-August 1918; 6 letters (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - F (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Fels, Mary, March-June 1918; 3 letters (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Field, Sara Bard, March-October 1918; 7 letters (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Fisher, Katherine, May-December 1918; 9 letters (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Flannigan, Minnie, March-November 1918; 11 letters (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Fligelma, Belle, 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - G (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Gann, Birdie, March-November 1918; 4 letters (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins, March-November 1918 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      10 letters. One letter signed by George Gilman.
    - Gram, Betty, July-September 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Granville-Smith, Jessica, March-November 1918; 39 letters (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Greenough, Jessie Lisle, October-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - H (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hays, J. W., October 20-22, 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Henkle, Alice, March-November 1918; 9 letters (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hilles, Florence Bayard, April-October 1918; 6 letters (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Hoge, Florence, March-April 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Hovey, Minnie, March-May 1918; 9 letters (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - I (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Ivins, Mrs. Delle R., October-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - J (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, Jennie, 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - K (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Katzenstein, Caroline, March-December 1918; 12 letters (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Kelz, Pearl, April-November 1918; 4 letters (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Kemble, Mrs. Tiny G., March-May 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. Miles, May 1, 1918; 4 telegrams (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Kent, Elizabeth, March-November 1918; 27 letters (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Kent, William, May-August 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Kerr, Lillian H., April-August 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - L (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Lambrose, Sarah Grant, March-November 1918; 4 letters (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Lapeen, Millie, August-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Laurendean, Lulu B., October 3-24, 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - LeDuc, Edith, April-June 1918; 4 letters (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Lefferts, Sara T., March-April 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Leilich, Martha E., November 4-5, 1918; 2 telegrams (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Lincoln, Katherine, May-November 1918; 25 letters (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Long, Margaret, March-December 1918; 51 letters (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Lowe, O.E., October-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Luce's Press Clipping Bureau, March-July 1918; 4 letters (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Lunsford, W.S., July-October 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - M (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Mallon, Winnifred, March-November 1918; 5 letters (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Malone, Dudley Field, August-October 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Martin, Harry, May-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Mead, Elwood, March-May 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Milholland, Vida, September-October 1918; 4 letters (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Mullen, Katherine, 1918; 11 letters (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - N (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - National Popular Government League, June-September 1918; 4 letters (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - National Voters' League (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Needham, Grace, April-May 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Nevada, Secretary of State, March-November 1918 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      7 letters. Signed by George Bordigan.
    - Nevada Women's Civic League, September 24-29, 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Nolen, Emma, May-July 1918; 21 letters (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Norcross, Frank Herbert, April-October 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Norton, Margaret, October-November 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - O (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Olmstead, Sue, March-April 1918; 3 letters (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Olzendam, Therese, May 4-13, 1918; 2 letters (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Ostrum, Ida, August 18-24, 1918; 4 telegrams (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - P (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Page, Mary Hutchison, March-April 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Patrick, Edward T., May-July 1918; 4 letters (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Paul, Alice, April-October 1918; 7 letters (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Pincus, Jane, March-September 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Pioche Record Publishing Company, March-June 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Pitzer, Annie A., 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Prohibition National Committee, March-October 1918 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      17 letters. Many signed by Virgil Hinshaw, chairman.
    - Public Ledger Company, March 4-8, 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Q (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - R (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Rasch, Frank W., October 22-25, 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Richardson, Mrs. S.M., April-May 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Riegel, Ella, April-November 1918; 34 letters (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Roach, Anna, October-November 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Rodman, Lillian E., August-September 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Romeike, Henry, March-April 1918; 4 letters (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Ross, Mrs. M., March-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Ross, Margery, March-October 1918; 4 letters (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Rowe, Clara Louise, March-May 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - S (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Sain, C.M., March-June 1918; 11 letters (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Schneiderman, Rose, April 15-29, 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Oscar J., March-September 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Spencer, Caroline E., March-July 1918; 4 letters (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Stevens, Doris, April-June 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Strengthen America Campaign, May 14-29, 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Summerfield, Mrs. Sardis, March 6, 1918; 2 telegrams (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Sykes, John, March-May 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - T (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Taylor, Mildred, April-July 1918; 7 letters (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Taylor, O. H., October-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Thatcher, George B., April-May 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Tonopah Daily Times, June-October 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Toohey, Katharine, August-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - V (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Valentine, Alice, November 6, 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Vernon, Mabel, May-December 1918; 44 letters (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - W (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Walsh, Frank Patrick, March-July 1918; 3 letters (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Weeks, Mrs. S.G. Sr., June-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - West, George P., April-August 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Western Railway Journal, October 7, 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - White, Grace, May-November 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Whittemore, Margaret, March-October 1918; 8 letters (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Whittemore, Mrs. Wright Nelson, 1918; 4 letters (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Willits, Mrs. S., May-June 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Wilson, Bird M., April-November 1918; 7 letters (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Wishon, Margaret, October-November 1918; 6 letters (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Wood, Charles Erskine Scott, September-October 1918; 4 letters (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Y (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Youmans, Florence G., September-October 1918; 2 telegrams (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Young, Mabel K., April-September 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Zadow, Mrs. Rudolf, March 1918; 2 letters (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Outgoing correspondence, March 1918-February 1919 (Box 16, Folder 1-13)
    - unidentified (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Campaign Correspondence, 1920; Sub-Series 3; Boxes 17-19
    - A (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Addams, Jane, June-September 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Advocate of Peace, April-May 1920 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      2 letters. Signed by George Perry Morris, assistant editor
    - Allen, Margaret, October 13-14, 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ackermann, Frances B., September-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, June-July 1920 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      7 letters. Some signed by Roger Baldwin.
    - Aston, Ann Penn, June-September 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - B (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Betty, G., August-September 1920; 4 letters (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Blatch, Harriott (Stanton), May-July 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Bright, Emily, September-October 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Brown, J.B., October 11-20, 1920; 2 telegrams (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Budd, G.L., October-November 1920; 4 letters (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Butler, Lizzie, July-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - C (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Caldwell, Robert J., May-October 1920; 5 letters (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Campbell, C.G., July-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Carlson, Theresa, March-November 1920; 8 letters (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Catt, Carrie Chapman, March-April 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Christensen, Parley Parker, September-October 1920; 9 letters (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Clark, W.C., August-November 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 21)